ILGWU Archives Department Collected Publications 5780/121 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- The Expulsion of the German Population from Czechoslovakia, 1960; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  v.4 of Documents on the Expulsion of the Germans from Eastern-Central-Europe
  - Item 1: The Expulsion of the German Population from Czechoslovakia, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Theodor Schieder. v.4 of Documents on the Expulsion of the Germans from Eastern-Central-Europe. Item is in German.
- Film Catalogue, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Film Catalogue, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). Item is in English.
- Financial and Statistical Report, 1953-1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  April 1, 1953 - March 31, 1956. Presented at the 29th Convention, Atlantic City, May 10, 1956. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Financial and Statistical Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By David Dubinsky. April 1, 1953 - March 31, 1956. Presented at the 29th Convention, Atlantic City, May 10, 1956. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Financial and Statistical Report, 1959-1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  January 1, 1959 - December 31, 1961. Presented at the 31st Convention, Atlantic City, May 23 0 June 1, 1962. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Financial and Statistical Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Louis Stulberg. January 1, 1959 - December 31, 1961. Presented at the 31st Convention, Atlantic City, May 23 0 June 1, 1962. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Financial Report: Employer Contributed Welfare Funds, 1962-1964; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  January 1, 1962 - December 31, 1964. Presented at the 32nd Convention, Miami Beach, Florida, 1965. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: Financial Report: Employer Contributed Welfare Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Louis Rolnick. January 1, 1962 - December 31, 1964. Presented at the 32nd Convention, Miami Beach, Florida, 1965. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- 1958 Financial Report of the Health, Welfare and Retirement Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  January 1, 1958 - December 31, 1958. Published May, 1959. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: 1958 Financial Report of the Health,Welfare and Retirement Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By GEB (General Executive Board). January 1, 1958 - December 31, 1958. Published May, 1959. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- 1960 Financial Report of the Health, Welfare Retirement and Supplemental Unemployment-Severance Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  January 1, 1960 - December 31, 1960. Published May, 1961. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: 1960 Financial Report of the Health, Welfare Retirement and Supplemental Unemployment-Severance Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By GEB (General Executive Board). January 1, 1960 - December 31, 1960. Published May, 1961. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- 1961 Financial Report of the Health, Welfare Retirement and Supplemental Unemployment-Severance Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  January 1, 1961 - December 31, 1961. Published May, 1962
  - Item 1: 1961 Financial Report of the Health, Welfare Retirement and Supplemental Unemployment-Severance Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By GEB (General Executive Board). January 1, 1961 - December 31, 1961. Published May, 1962. Item is in English.
- 1963 Financial Report of the Health and Welfare Retirement and Supplemental Unemployment-Severance Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  January 1, 1963 - December 31, 1963. Published May, 1964. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: 1963 Financial Report of the Health and Welfare Retirement and Supplemental Unemployment-Severance Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By GEB (General Executive Board). January 1, 1963 - December 31, 1963. Published May, 1964. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- 1964 Financial Report of the Health and Welfare Retirement and Supplemental Unemployment-Severance Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  January 1, 1964 - December 31, 1964. Published May, 1965.
  - Item 1: 1964 Financial Report of the Health and Welfare Retirement and Supplemental Unemployment-Severance Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By GEB (General Executive Board). January 1, 1964 - December 31, 1964. Published May, 1965. Item is in English.
- 1970 ILGWU Benefit Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  January 1, 1970 - December 31, 1970. Health and Welfare; Retirement; Supplemental Unemployment. Published 1971. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: 1970 ILGWU Benefit Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By GEB (General Executive Board). January 1, 1970 - December 31, 1970. Health and Welfare; Retirement; Supplemental Unemployment. Published 1971. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- 1973 ILGWU Benefit Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  January 1, 1973 - December 31, 1973. Health and Welfare; Retirement; Supplemental Unemployment. Published May 1974. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: 1973 ILGWU Benefit Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By GEB (General Executive Board). January 1, 1973 - December 31, 1973. Health and Welfare; Retirement; Supplemental Unemployment. Published May 1974. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- 1962 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: 1962 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Auditing Department. Item is in English.
- 1963 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: 1963 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 1964 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: 1964 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 1965 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: 1965 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Auditing Department. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- 1966 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  2 copies
  - Item 1: 1966 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    By Auditing Department. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- 1967 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: 1967 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 1969 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: 1969 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 1970 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: 1970 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
- 1971 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: 1971 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
- 1972 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: 1972 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 1973 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: 1973 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
- 1974 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: 1974 Financial Report: General Funds, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Friendly Visiting to the Aged in Institutions: A Program of Services for Retirees of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Friendly Visiting to the Aged in Institutions: A Program of Services for Retirees of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Der Funk, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Yiddish. Pages 9-12.
  - Item 1: Der Funk, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Pages 9-12. Item is in Yiddish.
- The Garment Carrier, 1955-1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  v.1:no.1,4,6,10,11 (1955-1957); v.1:no.11 (1958)
  - Item 1: The Garment Carrier, Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
    By Local 102. v.1:no.1,4,6,10,11 (1955-1957); v.1:no.11 (1958). Item is in English.
- The Garmentator, 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  v.2:no.1 (1944:Feb. 1)
  - Item 1: The Garmentator, Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    By Local 22. v.2:no.1 (1944:Feb. 1). Item is in English.
- Gerechtigkeit, 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
  v.31:no.15-16 (1949:Aug.). Justice.
  - Item 1: Gerechtigkeit, Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). v.31:no.15-16 (1949:Aug.). Justice. Item is in English.
- Giustizia, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
  Italian. v.16:no.4 (1934:Apr.) Justice.
  - Item 1: Giustizia, Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). v.16:no.4 (1934:Apr.) Jusitce. Item is in Italian.
- Good News, 1937-1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
  no.101,103,105-108
  - Item 1: Good News, Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). no.101,103,105-108. Item is in English.
- Grades and Body Prices Coats and Suits, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Spring, 1934
  - Item 1: Grades and Body Prices Coats and Suits, Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
    By Impartial Chairman Coat and Suit Industry. Spring, 1934. Item is in English.
- Guerra Fredda e Stabilizzazione Sociale., 1986; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  Italian. Doctoral dissertation
  - Item 1: Guerra Fredda e Stabilizzazione Sociale., Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    By Federico Romero. Doctoral dissertation. Item is in Italian.
- A History of the Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, 1927; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: A History of the Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    By James Oneal. Item is in English.
- A History of the Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, 1927; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  copy 2
  - Item 1: A History of the Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
    By James Oneal. copy 2. Item is in English.
- How City Voters are Shortchanged, 1963; Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
  The American Federationist, v.70:no.4 (1963: Apr.)
  - Item 1: How City Voters are Shortchanged, Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
    By Gus Tyler. The American Federationist, v.70:no.4 (1963: Apr.). Item is in English.
- How the Politburo Thinks by Leo Rosten; Letter to a Confused Liberal by J. B. S. Hardman, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  Rosten reprinted from Look magazine, March 13, 1951. Hardman reprinted form Labor and Nation. 2 copies
  - Item 1: How the Politburo Thinks by Leo Rosten; Letter to a Confused Liberal by J. B. S. Hardman, Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
    By Leo Rosten; J. B. S. Hardman. Rosten reprinted from Look magazine, March 13, 1951. Hardman reprinted form Labor and Nation. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- ILGWU Death Benefit Fund, 1962; Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
  Article 13 of the Constitution of the ILGWU. As amended to July 1, 1962. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: ILGWU Death Benefit Fund, Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
    By Death Benefit Fund Department. Article 13 of the Constitution of the ILGWU. As amended to July 1, 1962. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- ILGWU Guide on Agreement Provisions, Standards and Enforcement, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
  Reprinted from Justice, July 1, 1965
  - Item 1: ILGWU Guide on Agreement Provisions, Standards and Enforcement, Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). Reprinted from Justice, July 1, 1965. Item is in English.
- ILGWU News Bulletin, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
  v.1:no.3 (1956:Mar.)
  - Item 1: ILGWU News Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
    By Locals 166-222. v.1:no.3 (1956:Mar.). Item is in English.
- The ILGWU Speaks Out For Undocumented Workers, 1980; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
  Testimony by ILGWU Vice President Jay Mazar at a hearing in New York City of the Select Commission on Immigration and Refugee Policy, January 21, 1980. 3 copies.
  - Item 1: The ILGWU Speaks Out For Undocumented Workers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
    By Jay Mazar. Testimony by ILGWU Vice President Jay Mazar at a hearing in New York City of the Select Commission on Immigration nad Refugee Policy, January 21, 1980. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Impartial Chairman Coat and Suit Industry: James J. Walker, 1940-1941, Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Impartial Chairman Coat and Suit Industry: James J. Walker, 1940-1941, Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
    By James J. Walker. Item is in English.
- Impartial Chairman Coat and Suit Industry: James J. Walker, 1942-1945; Harry L. Hopkins, 1945-1946, 1942-1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Impartial Chairman Coat and Suit Industry: James J. Walker, 1942-1945; Harry L. Hopkins, 1945-1946, Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
    By James J. Walker; Harry L. Hopkins. Item is in English.
- Important Bulletin of Local 117, ILGWU, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
  v.1:no.1 (1965:Jan. 20)
  - Item 1: Important Bulletin of Local 117, ILGWU, Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
    By Local 117. v.1:no.1 (1965:Jan. 20). Item is in English.
- In Shap un Oysern Shap, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Yiddish
  - Item 1: In Shap un Oysern Shap, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Menashe Zinkin. Item is in Yiddish.
- In the District Court of Appeals, State of California: Petition for Writ of Prohibition, 1943; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: In the District Court of Appeals, State of California: Petition for Writ of Prohibition, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Emil Schlesinger. Item is in English.
- In the District Court of Appeals, State of California: Brief and Points and Authorities in Support of Petition for Writ of Prohibition, 1943; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: In the District Court of Appeals, State of California: Brief and Points and Authorities in Support of Petition for Writ of Prohibition, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
- In the Matter of: National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: In the Matter of: National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Alexander Printz; David Dubinsky. Item is in English.
- In the Superior Court of the State of California: Opening Brief of Defendant, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, on Motions to Quash Alleged Service of Summons., 1943; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: In the Superior Court of the State of California: Opening Brief of Defendant, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, on Motions to Quash Alleged Service of Summons., Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
- In the Superior Court of the State of California: Reply Brief of Defendant, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, on Motions to Quash Alleged Service of Summons., 1943; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: In the Superior Court of the State of California: Relpy Brief of Defendant, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, on Motions to Quash Alleged Service of Summons., Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
- In the Supreme Court of the United States: Brief for Appellants, 1937; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: In the Supreme Court of the United States: Brief for Appellants, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By Frank P. Walsh; Jerome Walsh. Item is in English.
- In the Supreme Court of the United States: Brief on Behalf of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, As Amicus Curiae, 1938; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: In the Supreme Court of the United States: Brief on Behalf of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, As Amicus Curiae, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    By Elias Lieberman. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- In the Supreme Court of the United States: Reply Brief for Appellants, 1937; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: In the Supreme Court of the United States: Reply Brief for Appellants, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
- In the United States Circuit Court of Appeals: Brief for the Administrator of the Wage and Hour Division, United States Department of Labor., 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: In the United States Circuit Court of Appeals: Brief for the Administrator of the Wage and Hour Division, United States Department of Labor., Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    By Gerard D. Reilly; Irving J. Levy; Alex Elson; Edward Jay Fruchtman; Lee K. Beznor; Sidney A. Jones, Jr. Item is in English.
- Industrial Court of the Cloak, Suit, and Skirt Industry in New York City, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  In Bulletin of the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics, no.144 (1914:Mar. 19)
  - Item 1: Industrial Court of the Cloak, Suit, and Skirt Industry in New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Charles H. Winslow. In Bulletin of the U.S. Bureaur of Labor Statistics, no.144 (1914:Mar. 19). Item is in English.
- Information and Instructions for Local Union Office Managers on Procedures Relating to the ILGWU Death Benefit Fund, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Information and Instructions for Local Union Office Managers on Procedures Relating to the ILGWU Death Benefit Fund, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    By Death Benefit Fund Department. Item is in English.
- The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1939; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Reprinted from Labor Information Bulletin, August 1939.
  - Item 1: The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By Max D. Danish. Reprinted from Labor Information Bulletin, August 1939. Item is in English.
- The Jew and Communism, 1919-1941, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Jew and Communism, 1919-1941, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Melech Epstein. Item is in English.
- The Jewish Labor Movement in America: Two Views., 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Jewish Labor Movement in New York, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By William Morris Leiserson. Thesis submitted for Bachelor of Arts degree. Item is in English.
- The Jewish Labor Movement in New York, 1908; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Thesis submitted for Bachelor of Arts degree
  - Item 1: The Jewish Labor Movement in America: Two Views., Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By Israel Knox; Irving Howe. Item is in English.
- The Jewish People: Past and Present, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  v.2
  - Item 1: The Jewish People: Past and Present, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    By Jewish Encyclopedic Handbooks. v.2. Item is in English.
- The Jewish People: Past and Present, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  v.3
  - Item 1: The Jewish People: Past and Present, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    By Jewish Encyclopedic Handbooks. v.3. Item is in English.
- Joint Board Cloakmakers' Union of New York Thirty-Fifth Anniversary Jubilee Book, 1910-1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Cover embossed: M. Kraus
  - Item 1: Joint Board Cloakmakers' Union of New York Thirty-Fifth Anniversary Jubilee Book, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Cover embossed: M. Kraus. Item is in English.
- Der Klouk Finisher, 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Yiddish and English. The Cloak Finisher. v.1:no.1-2,4-5 (1942)
  - Item 1: Der Klouk Finisher, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    By Local 9. The Cloak Finisher. v.1:no.1-2,4-5 (1942). Item is in English; Yiddish.
- Klouk-Finishers Voice, 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Yiddish and English. Cloak-Finishers Voice. v.1:no.1 (1942:Jan. 12)
  - Item 1: Klouk-Finishers Voice, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    By Local 9. Cloak-Finishers Voice. v.1:no.1 (1942:Jan. 12). Item is in English; Yiddish.
- Der Klouk un Dressmaker, 1931; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Yiddish. v.1:no.1-3 (1931)
  - Item 1: Der Klouk un Dresmaker, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    By Left Wing Opposition. v.1:no.1-3 (1931). Item is in Yiddish.
- Knit Goods News, 1961; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  v.12:no.9 (1961:Apr. 24)
  - Item 1: Knit Goods News, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    By Local 190. v.12:no.9 (1961:Apr. 24). Item is in English.
- Knitgoods Workers Voice, 1941-1987; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
  v.5:no.5-6 (1941); v.9:no.1 (1945); v.12:no.1,4 (1948); v.14:no.1-3,5-6,8 (1950); v.15:no.1,3-5 (1951); v.16:no.6 (1953); v.17:no.2,4 (1954); v.19:no.1 (1956); v.20:no.3-4 (1957); v.21:no.1-2,4 (1958); v.46:no.1 (1984), v.47:no.3 (1986); v.48:no.1 (1987)
  - Item 1: Knitgoods Workers Voice, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    By Local 155. v.5:no.5-6 (1941); v.9:no.1 (1945); v.12:no.1,4 (1948); v.14:no.1-3,5-6,8 (1950); v.15:no.1,3-5 (1951); v.16:no.6 (1953); v.17:no.2,4 (1954); v.19:no.1 (1956); v.20:no.3-4 (1957); v.21:no.1-2,4 (1958); v.46:no.1 (1984), v.47:no.3 (1986); v.48:no.1 (1987). Item is in English.
- Labor in the Metropolis, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Labor in the Metropolis, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
    By Gus Tyler. Item is in English.
- Labor Organization Annual Report: Form LM-2 and Instructions, 1967; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Labor Organization Annual Report: Form LM-2 and Instructions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    By Office of Labor-Management and Welfare-Pension Reports. Item is in English.
- The Ladies' Garment Worker, 1913; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  English and Yiddish. v.4:no.1-12 (1913). Bound volume
  - Item 1: The Ladies' Garment Worker, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). v.4:no.1-12 (1913). Bound volume. Item is in English; Yiddish.
- Let's Go! Manual for Education Committees, ILGWU, 1955; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Let's Go! Manual for Education Committees, ILGWU, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Lincoln Center Stagebill, 1985; Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Entertainment for ILGWU Retirees, October 29, 1985.
  - Item 1: Lincoln Center Stagebill, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Entertainment for ILGWU Retirees, October 29, 1985. Item is in English.
- Live, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Live, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    By David Dubinsky. Item is in English.
- Local 132 News, 1957; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  v.1:no.3 (1957:May)
  - Item 1: Local 132 News, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    By Local 132. v.1:no.3 (1957:May). Item is in English.
- Local 22 Union School Spring 1938 Catalogue, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Local 22 Union School Spring 1938 Catalogue, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    By Local 22. Item is in English.
- Local 23-25 News, 1985; Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
  v.34:no.3 (1985:Nov.)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
    By Local 23-25. v.34:no.3 (1985:Nov.). Item is in English.
- Local 35 News, 1958-1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
  English and Yiddish. v.2:no.1 (1958:Apr.); v.3:no.1 (1959:Jan.); v.7:no.3 (1963:Oct.); v.8:no.3 (1964:June); v.9:no.2 (1965:Oct.)
  - Item 1: Local 35 News, Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
    By Local 35. v.2:no.1 (1958:Apr.); v.3:no.1 (1959:Jan.); v.7:no.3 (1963:Oct.); v.8:no.3 (1964:June); v.9:no.2 (1965:Oct.). Item is in English; Yiddish.
- The Lock-Out in the Cloak and Suit Industry, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
  The Record of a Public Hearing before Mayor John Purroy Mitchell at the City Hall, New York, April 26th, 1916.
  - Item 1: The Lock-Out in the Cloak and Suit Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    The Record of a Public Hearing before Mayor John Purroy Mitchell at the City Hall, New York, April 26th, 1916. Item is in English.
- Meeting of the Board of Arbitrators, 1913; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
  October 12 and 13, 1913
  - Item 1: Meeting of the Board of Arbitrators, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    October 12 and 13, 1913. Item is in English.
- The Needle Point, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Needle Point, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
    By Local 249. Item is in English.